faysalbank.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy Statement | Faysal Bank

This web site is administered by Faysal Bank Limited.

When you visit this web site Faysal Bank Limited (“Faysal Bank”) may collect personal data about you, either directly (where you are asked to provide the data) or indirectly. Faysal Bank will, however, only use the personal data in accordance with the purpose set forth in this Privacy Statement and is committed to safeguarding the personal information collected. This statement sets out the purpose of Faysal Bank data processing in respect of this web site, the use of cookies and how to affect your rights in respect of your personal data.

Purposes of Processing: Faysal Bank collects and processes information about customers and visitors to its web site to conduct its business, to inform and make available products and services that may be of interest to you and for the development of web statistics. The information you provide will be used to contact you when necessary, e.g. to notify you about functionality changes to the web site and to offer services that you may find helpful (provided you have not opted out to receive such services).

Sensitive Data: Faysal Bank does not seek to collect sensitive personal data (such as data revealing political opinions, religious beliefs, health or other matters) through this site. If Faysal Bank does seek to collect such data, your prior consent thereto will be asked. Please note that, by providing Faysal Bank with unsolicited sensitive personal data you consent to our using such data as described above.

Cookies: Faysal Bank may gather and analyze information regarding usage of this web site, including domain name, the number of hits, the pages visited, previous/subsequent sites visited and length of user session. This information may be gathered via Java script and persisted by using a cookie. A cookie is a small text file placed on your hard drive by our web page server. You can choose whether or not to use a cookie by altering the settings of your browser. A cookie will make the use of this web site faster and easier. Faysal Bank Limited may disclose and transfer any information that is collected via this website to any company with its affiliates, agents or information provider or if we have a duty or right to disclose or are compelled to do so by law.

Third Party Sites: Please note that this Privacy Statement does not extend to third party sites linked to this web site.

Amendments: Faysal Bank reserves the right to modify sections of this Privacy Statement at any time. Please check this statement from time to time for any changes.
